Google Analytics reports on all the interactions of users with a site or an app.
Google Analytics 能够报告用户与网站或应用的所有互动
However, in order for that to happen the owner of a site
然而要想获得此报告
needs to integrate Google Analytics code in the web site or app.
网站所有者需要将 Google Analytics 代码集成到其网站或应用中
Google Analytics code is a piece of
Google Analytics 代码是一小段
Javascript that gets integrated in the rest of the code of the site.
需要集成至其他网站代码中的 Javascript 代码
Every page of a website needs to have that code in order
网站的每个页面都需要集成这段代码
for Google Analytics to track the activity on that page.
以便 Google Analytics 跟踪相应页面上发生的活动
This piece of Javascript will then instruct to that page to send
这段 Javascript 代码将指示相应页面
relevant data to Google Analytics so that it can be included for reporting.
向 Google Analytics 发送需包含在分析报告中的相关数据
For mobile apps the general principle is the same, however,
对于移动应用 基本集成原理也是一样的
instead of Javascript the app owner needs to integrate the code via an SDK,
但移动应用所有者需要通过 SDK 来集成这段代码 而不是使用 Javascript
which stands for Software Development Kit,
SDK 就是软件开发套件
a special piece of software,
应用开发者可将这种特殊的软件
app developers can integrate in their app to connect it to other platforms,
集成到自己的应用中 以便与其他平台建立连接
in this case Google Analytics.
现在我们指的就是 Google Analytics 平台
Also, mobile apps don't really work with pages so
另外 我们在移动应用中实际上不是跟踪页面
instead we track activities in Mobile and thus,
而是跟踪手机中发生的活动
some code needs to be added to every possible activity.
所以我们需要为所有可能发生的活动添加一些代码
Once the Google Analytics code is integrated in a site or an app,
将 Google Analytics 代码集成到网站或应用中后
Google will start collecting data on
Google 便会开始收集
the interaction of the users with the site or the app.
有关用户与网站或应用互动的数据
Google makes it very easy to integrate this code in your site.
Google 让我们能够轻松地将此代码集成到网站中
In most cases a website developer will take care of that for you.
在多数情况下 网站开发者将帮助你完成集成
In case you have a website that's built in a platform like,
如果你的网站架设在
for instance, Squarespace, Wix, WordPress, etc.
Squarespace、Wix 以及 WordPress 等平台上
integration with Google Analytics is usually already built in.
他们通常内置集成了 Google Analytics
In case you need to do this yourself for your site,
如果你需要自己动手为网站实施此集成
you will find the following walk through by just in controlling at Google helpful.
那么观看以下由 Google 提供的讲解视频将很有帮助
If you won't be the one setting this up you can skip the next video.
如果你无需负责执行此集成操作 则可以跳过下一个视频